

CONTACT ME AT

+48 513 064 975

danyah.bougsiaa@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

✓ English- Fluent

✓ Polish- Mother tounge

E D U C A T I O N A L H I S T O R Y

Boston Berklee College of Music

Summer Performance Program| Jan 2013 - Dec 2014

Gdańsk Music Academy Graduate

Bachelor in Jazz and Stage Music | Jan 2013 - Dec 2014

AWARDS RECEIVED

Sopot President's scholarship for achivements in music

DANYAH BOUGSIAA

PERSONAL PROFILE

Dedicated to self development in the work and personal space. Owing to experience in customer service appointed with great communication and problem solving skills as well as attentive listening. Furthermore highly adaptable, flexible due to the work environment in Music Studio in addition to leadership abilities acquired as a Tour/Band manager. Enriches the work structure with own initiative by being a dedicated team player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-owner and Manager

Music Studio (Poland) | 2015-2016

- Accomplishing objectives by managing staff; planning and evaluating activities. Developing personal growth opportunities.
- Ensuring a safe, secure, and legal work environment.
- Accomplishing staff results by communicating job expectations; planning, monitoring, and appraising job results. Contributing to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.
- Coaching, counseling, and disciplining employees.
- Establishing strategic goals
- Defining objectives, identifying and evaluating trends and options, choosing a course of action, and evaluating outcomes.
- Maintaining quality service by enforcing quality and customer service standards, analyzing and resolving quality and customer service problems, and recommending system improvements.

Advertising, Customer Service and Sales Person

Apllovez (Netherlands), Oriflame, Dom Sushi, Barocco, Ciuciu, Pierogi, Telepizza (Poland) | 2011-2019

- Acquiring new clients.
- Maintaining a positive, empathetic and professional attitude toward customers at all times.
- Responding promptly to customer inquiries. Processing orders, forms, applications, and requests.
- Communicating with customers through various channels.
- Acknowledging and resolving customer complaints.
- Knowing our products inside and out so that you can answer questions.
- Keeping records of customer interactions, transactions, comments and complaints.
- Communicating and coordinating with colleagues as necessary.
- Providing feedback on the efficiency of the customer service process.
- Ensuring customer satisfaction and providing professional customer support.

Medical Receptionist

Ocus (Poland) | 2011, 2018

- Serving patients by greeting and helping them, scheduling appointments, and maintaining records and accounts.
- Welcoming patients and visitors in person or on the telephone, and answering or referring inquiries.
- Optimising patients satisfaction
- Keeping patient appointments on schedule by notifying provider of patient's arrival, reviewing service delivery compared to schedule, and reminding providers of service delays.
- Comforting patients by anticipating patients' anxieties, answering patients' questions, and maintaining the reception area.
- Ensuring availability of treatment information by filing and retrieving patient records.
- Maintaining patient accounts by obtaining, recording, and updating personal and financial information.
- Protecting patients rights by maintaining confidentiality of medical, personal, and financial information.
- Maintaining operations by following policies and procedures, reporting needed changes.

Tour manager, Band Leader, Musician, Voice Teacher

Elek3city, Ptaki Maja Fraze and more (Poland) | 2010-2020

- Organising rehearsal space and time
- Promoting the band
- Sending out offers through different platforms (email, phone,Fb, Instagram, personally), managing band pages (Fb, Instagram)
- Dealing with promoters, venue managers, ticket agents, owners and the like
- Promoting and setting concert dates
- Confirming reservations
- Managing tour finances
- Transporting band members and taking care of the musical repertoir

Babysitter, Private English Teacher for children, Horse Riding Instructor for disabled children

Kolibki (Poland) | 2011, 2019

- Taking care of children, educating them, disciplining, teaching english through play time
- Cleaning the stable and preparing the horses for work, assisting disabled children, instructing and coordinating the riding lessons

Agriculture worker and cleaning services

Tomaszulka Eco Farm (Poland) | 2017

- Taking care of the harvest
- Baking bread and pastry
- Collecting and packaging fruit/vegetables/bread & pastry
- Cleaning the farm and household
- Managing other cleaning workers